McCann Postcard Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Postcards collected by Agnes McCann, 1; 1 linear feet Box: 1 Folder: 1 Number of items: 420
  - Lake Drive in Gordon Park, Cleveland, Ohio. Jul 25, 1906., 302 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Garfield Memorial, Cleveland, Ohio. Sept. 14, 1904., 303 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The Rookery.” Chicago, Illinois. Jan. 6, 1906., 304 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Broadway, Chambers St. and City Hall, New York. 1905., 305 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - State and Madison Sts. Chicago. Sep., 190?., 306 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Five Cascades, Haines Falls, Catskill Mountains. Jul. 1905., 307 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cape Eternity and Trinity. Aug. 25, 1905., 308 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - St. Margaret’s Church, Staatsburg, N.Y. Jul. 27, ?., 309 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Spring Point Light, Portland Harbor., 310 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Sunnyside of Washington Irving.” (Below Tarrytown.) Sep. 6, 1904., 311 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Elevator. Montreal. Aug. 25, 1905., 312 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Boardwalk, Ashbury Park, N.J. Aug. 5, 1903., 313 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Johnston Gate and Surroundings- Harvard University. Jul. 13, 1906., 314 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. (Butterfly letter card.) Sep. 1, 1905., 315 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Cupid’s Don’ts.” Feb. 14., 316 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Easter Greetings.” Apr. 14, 1906., 317 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Universitas Pennsylvaniensis”. May 1, 1906., 318 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “I’m Having a Nice Time Here.” (Riddle card.) Aug. 14, 1905., 319 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Puzzle. Mar. 3, 1906., 320 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Immaculate Conception Cathedral, Albany, N.Y. Aug. 12, 190?., 321 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vassar Chapel, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Nov. 12, 1906., 322 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - La Danza D’Apollo Con Le Muse., 323 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Mille Felicitazioni.”, 324 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Post Office, cor. 4th and Broadway, Troy, N.Y. Jan. 1907., 325 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Highland Avenue, Middletown, N.Y. Dec. 19, 1907., 326 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Esposizione Di Milano-1906. Bulgaria. Nov. 24, 1906., 327 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Empire Building. N.Y City. Dec. 18, 1906., 328 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Town Hall, Great Barrington, Mass. Jun. 28, 1906., 329 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled., 330 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled., 331 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Flower Beds, Prospect Park, Brooklyn N.Y. Oct. 16, 1906., 332 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled., 333 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled., 334 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ocean Parkway, Entrance to Prospect Park, Brooklyn, N.Y. Oct. 15, 1906., 335 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cutrin Statue and Soldiers Memorial, Bellefonte, P.A. Jan. 2, 1907., 336 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vassar Lake, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Jan. 18, 1907., 337 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Park Hotel, Williamsport, P.A. Mar. 12., 338 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Oldest Hotel in the U.S. Established 1732. The Rhinebeck Hotel. Rhinebeck, N.Y. Feb. 7, 1907., 339 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Acnes.” Nov. 10, 190?., 340 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Court House, West Third St., looking East, Williamsport, P.A. Mar. 12, 1907., 341 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Thanksgiving.” Nov. 12, 1906., 342 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. Apr. 14, 190?., 343 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Hopping Good Time.” Jun. 29, 1907., 344 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The Music Master.” “The Auctioneer.” Dec. 3, 1906., 345 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Everything Looks Dark Here.” Jun. 29, 1907., 346 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Eagle Hotel, 18-32 Main Street, Kingston, N.Y., 347 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Court House, Troy, N.Y. Jun. 26, 1907., 348 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - River Street, Troy, N.Y. Jun. 26, 1907., 349 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Third Street from Fulton St. looking South, Troy, N.Y. Jun. 26, 1907., 350 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Samaritan Hospital, Troy, N.Y. Jun. 26, 1907., 351 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Largest Water Wheel in the World. Burden Mill, Troy, N.Y. Jun. 26, 1907., 352 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Manhattan College, N.Y. Jun. 1907., 353 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Best Wishes For a Happy New Year.” Dec. 1906., 354 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Merry Christmas to All.” Dec. 22, 1906., 355 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “1907, A Happy New Year.” Dec. 31, 1906., 356 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Note From Newburgh, N.Y.” (Letter Enclosed.), 357 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Joyful Easter.” Mar. 30, 1907., 358 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Happy New Year to You All.” Jan. 2, 1907., 359 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Easter Greetings.” 1907., 360 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “How do you do!” Mar. 28., 361 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “With Valentine Greetings.” Feb. 14, 1907., 362 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “From One Who Thinks of Thee.” Feb 13, 1907., 363 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Best Easter Wishes.” Mar. 1907., 364 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “With Best Christmas Wishes.” The Messenger Boy. Dec. 24, 1908., 365 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Friendship’s Token.”, 366 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Merry Christmas.” Dec. 24, 1907., 367 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “La Nativite’.”, 368 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled., 369 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “God Bless You and Keep You.” Dec. 24, 1908., 370 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “New Year Greetings.” Dec. 31, 1907., 371 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Happy New Year.” Dec. 31, 1908., 372 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “A Token of Love.”, 373 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “To My Valentine.” Feb. 4, 1906., 374 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “My Thoughts Are of Thee.” Feb. 14, 1907., 375 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Breakwater Light Portland Harbor, Portland, M.E., 376 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Randolph St., East from La Salle St., Chicago. Jul. 10, 1905., 377 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acquario, Arch Locati. May 1906., 378 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Down Broadway From Dun Building, New York., 379 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stamford, N.Y. Trappers Lodge, Lake&Honeymoon Cottage in Churchill Park. Aug. 13, 1907., 380 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Navigazione Generale Italiana. May 1906., 381 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Park Lake Bridge, Albany, N.Y. Aug. 11, 1907., 382 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Greetings from Rockaway. Lifeguards to the Rescue. Aug. 13, 1907., 383 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - St. John’s R.C. Church, Paterson, N.J. Oct. 12, 1905., 384 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arti Decorative Francesi. Arch Bongi. May 1906., 385 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cosmopolitan New York. “Chinatown in Mott Street.” Apr. 22, 1905., 386 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Owasco Road, Auburn N.Y. 1907., 387 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Breakers at Rockaway Beach, N.Y. Aug. 13, 1907., 388 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - First National Bank, Main Street, Looking South, Port Allegany, PA. Jan. 20, 190?., 389 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hall of Records and City Hall Park, New York., 390 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Norddeutscher Lloyd, Bremen. Gruss von Bord des Dampfers, Prinzess Irene., 391 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “You had better take a tumble and write to.” Mar. 27, 1907., 392 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - River Street, Troy, N.Y. Apr. 2, 1907., 393 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Tis the wise that visit.” Mar. 25, 1907., 394 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Not Labeled. Aug. 25, 1901., 395 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Manhattan College, N.Y. Apr. 10, 1901., 396 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Court Square, Springfield, Mass. Jun. 2, 1907., 397 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Tuesday. This Little Bear Irons Clothes.” Apr. 13, 1907., 398 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Washington Bridge, N.Y. City. Jun. 1, 1907., 399 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Troy Looking South, Troy, N.Y. May 13, 1907., 400 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - New York and Pennsylvania Co’s. Paper Mills, Johnsonburg, P.A. Jul. 13, 1907., 401 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clark’s Landing, Point Pleasant, N.J. Jul. 1907., 402 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lawns and Gardens, Mohonk Lake, N.Y. Aug. 2, 1907., 403 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - West Shokan Village, (High Point in the Distance), Catskill Mts. Aug. 2, 1907., 404 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bathing Scene at Pavilion. Point Pleasant, N.J. Jul. 18, 1907., 405 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ruins of Fort Ticonderoga, Lake Champlain, N.Y. Aug. 1, 1907., 406 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Where ignorance is bliss ‘tis a folly to be wise.” Apr. 18, 1907., 407 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - High Rock, 2000 Ft. above Sea Level. The Northville Bridge over the Saganda River. Aug. 5, 1907., 408 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Union School Building, Fort Edward, N.Y. Aug. 3, 1907., 409 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sunset on Connecticut River, Springfield Mass. Aug. 9, 1907., 410 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Whitehall Building, New York. Aug. 8, 1907., 411 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - White Lake as seen from the Outlet. July 23, 1907., 412 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - President Roosevelt Cottage, Campobello Island, N.B., 413 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Madison Square Garden, New York. Aug. 3, 1907., 414 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Favorite Walk, Catholic Summer School, Cliff Haven, Lake Champlain, N.Y. Aug. 8, 1907., 415 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Canoeing in the Adirondacks, Long Lake, New York. Jul. 1907., 416 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Memorial House, New Paltz, N.Y. Jul. 12, 1907., 417 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Summer School, Cliff Haven, Lake Champlain, N.Y. Aug. 8, 1907., 418 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Wappingers Creek at Pleasant Valley, N.Y. Aug. 1907., 419 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ariel Bridge, Duluth, Minn. Aug. 7, 1907., 420 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 2. Miscellaneous, 2; 0.1 linear feet Box: 1 Folder: 1 Number of items: 1
  Series contains a book, From Ocean to Ocean, distributed by the Mitchell Motor Car Company, which describes how a car, The Mitchell Ranger, carried the First Transcontinental War Dispatch. From Major- General Leonard Wood in New York to Major- General John F. Weston in San Francisco.
  - From Ocean to Ocean: How The Mitchell Ranger carried the First Transcontinental War Dispatch. Racine, Wisconsin: The Mitchell Motor Car Company., 421 (Box 1, Folder 1)